"addon"
{
	"addonname"										"SUPER SMASH DOTA"
	// Loading screen/settings/help etc
	"DirectionalMovement_Title" "Direction Movement"
	"DirectionalMovement_Body" "Character movement is done with the keys. \nPress 'W' to jump up to two times. \nPress 'S' to drop from a ledge."
	"MouseUsage_Body" "Each color/direction functions as button"
	"MouseUsage_Title" "Mouse Usage"
	"Contribute_Title" "Contribute?"
	"Contribute_Body" "I am always looking for feedback, graphical, technical or gameplay. If this is not written in your language and you want to translate, you are very welcome! Other help might also be very welcome."
	"Wiki_Title" "Wiki"
	"Wiki_Body" "For more detailed information about Super Smash Dota visit the wiki!"
	"Start_Title" "Start"
	"Start_Body" "You can still vote for 5 seconds once someone presses this, be quick!"
	"Special_Title" "Special Attacks"
	"Special_Body" "Every hero has three unique moves, use them with your right mouse while having your mouse in a colored box. \n\nSpells with a red outline require to be held."
	"Shield_Title" "Shield"
	"Shield_Body" "You get a regenerating shield you can use to negate effects from spells. \n\nRight click in the middle to activate."
	"Attacks_Title" "Basic Attacks"
	"Attacks_Body" "Every hero has the same attacks, a quick attack can be cast by clicking in the middle. \n\nDiretional attacks are cast in a direction and can be charged by holding your mouse."
	"Settings_Title" "Settings"
	"Gamemode" "Gamemode"
	"FFA" "Free for all"
	"2v2" "2 v 2"
	"HeroSelection" "Hero Selection"
	"AP" "All Pick"
	"AR" "All Random"
	"Thanks" "Thank you for playing"
	"Changelog_Body"	"1.03: \n\nAdded Techies \nRebalanced special jump skills."
	"Changelog_Title"	"Changelog:"
	
	// Ally pick screen
	"ChooseAlly"									"CHOOSE YOUR ALLY"
	
	// Hero pick screen
	// Rating things

	"Disables" 										"Disables"
	"Cooldowns" 									"Cooldowns"
	"Animations" 									"Animations"
	"Knockback" 									"Knockback"
	"Damage" 										"Damage"
	"Evasiveness"									"Evasiveness"
	"Likelyness" 									"Likelyness to hit"
	
	// Random
	"npc_dota_hero__bio" "Randoming does not only surprise your enemies, but also 
yourself!"

	// Puck
    "npc_dota_hero_puck" "Puck"
    "npc_dota_hero_puck_bio" "Puck is great at evading it's foes and reacting before they were ready. Puck can hurt them from distance, silence units around it, remove itself temporarily from the game and send an orb to which it can jaunt at any point."
	"AbilityTooltip_puck_special_side" "Puck fires a little explosion, damaging and silencing the units around it in a small area." 
	"AbilityTooltip_puck_special_top" "Puck fires a projectile, if a projectile exists casting this spell will move puck to the projectile location. Takes cursor position into account."
	"AbilityTooltip_puck_special_bottom" "Puck temporarily dissappears, unable to take any damage"
	
	// Tusk
    "npc_dota_hero_tusk" "Tuskar"
    "npc_dota_hero_tusk_bio" "Tuskar has excellent mobility due to his snowball, which he exploits with hard kicks. Can even use his sigil to lift him up and slow enemies."
	"AbilityTooltip_tusk_special_side" "Tuskar kicks everything in front of him pushing them back and dealing some damage" 
	"AbilityTooltip_tusk_special_top" "Tuskar creates a sigil to lift him up and slowing nearby enemies"
	"AbilityTooltip_tusk_special_bottom" "Tuskar becomes a snowball, dealing minor damage to every units it touches. Breaks on any order"	
	
	// Lina
    "npc_dota_hero_lina" "Lina"
    "npc_dota_hero_lina_bio" "Lina may not be the quickest caster, but noone likes being hit by her spells. Laguna blade hurts so much you wished you paid attention, while Light Strike Array is no joke either, to top it all of Lina can lift her up with one of her favorite items."
	"AbilityTooltip_lina_special_bottom" "Lina fires an array from above, stunning and damaging everyone on impact" 
	"AbilityTooltip_lina_special_side" "Lina fires a projectile so heavy it stuns her while casting. Deals heavy damage towards every unit in its way."
	"AbilityTooltip_lina_special_top" "Lina uses her beloved Eul's scepter and flies safely up in the air for a short moment."
	
	
	// Earthshaker
    "npc_dota_hero_earthshaker" "Earthshaker"
    "npc_dota_hero_earthshaker_bio" "Earthshaker loves a platformer, he has the power to shake all the platforms. Seeing how earthshaker acts it's not the jump that hurts but the landing. To finish this off he has a good punch. Needless to say, Earthshaker knows how to stun his foes."
	"AbilityTooltip_earthshaker_special_side" "Earthshaker smashes his enemy brutally providing heavy knockback." 
	
	"AbilityTooltip_earthshaker_special_top" "Earthshaker jumps up, but it's not the jump, but the landing that is dangerous. Stuns and damages targets around him
on landing"
	"AbilityTooltip_earthshaker_special_bottom" "Earthshaker uses all of his force to hit everyone on a platform, stunning and damaging them"
	
	// Clockwerk
    "npc_dota_hero_rattletrap" "Clockwerk"
    "npc_dota_hero_rattletrap_bio" "Clockwerk may have a long reach, but the hero excels at short range combo with his annoying battery assault. Getting close might not be a problem with his hookshot."
	"AbilityTooltip_rattletrap_special_bottom" "Clockwerk uses his battery assault, dealing minor damage to random targets around him." 
	"AbilityTooltip_rattletrap_special_side" "Clockwerk fires a rocket, preferably with great precision. Dealing damage to everyone around the explosion. Does always reach destination. Takes cursor position into account."
	"AbilityTooltip_rattletrap_special_top" "Clockwerk shoots his hook in the air, to see if he can hit someone, will always pull up but if a target is hit it takes damage. Takes cursor position into account."
	
	
	// Zuus
    "npc_dota_hero_zuus" "Zeus"
    "npc_dota_hero_zuus_bio" "Zeus is no stranger to battles and doesn't stay away from this one either. He is able to manipulate the clouds by going into them, but most importantly he is able to create those epic thunderstrikes everyone expects him to, he can hit units in front of him or even everyone at the same time. Finally he has some tricks to create bouncing thunderstrikes."
	"AbilityTooltip_zuus_special_bottom" "Zeus strikes the ground in front of him, hurting enemies who happen to be there." 
	"AbilityTooltip_zuus_special_side" "Zeus creates a bouncing projectile, get's destroyed if it hits a target or loses it's platform."
	"AbilityTooltip_zuus_special_top" "Zeus blinks into the cloud, order it to thunderstrike a moment later!"
	
	
	// Mirana
    "npc_dota_hero_mirana" "Mirana"
    "npc_dota_hero_mirana_bio" "Mirana is once again extremely mobile and versatile, snipe with arrows from afar, or hit targets with starfall. Leap gives insane mobility to try and do both at 
the same time."
	"AbilityTooltip_mirana_special_bottom" "Mirana uses her powers of the night and drops stars, on her nearby enemies. One unlucky foe get's double stars." 
	"AbilityTooltip_mirana_special_side" "Mirana fires her famous arrow, damaging her targets and 	stunning based on the distance the arrow travelled. Takes cursor position into account."
	"AbilityTooltip_mirana_special_top" "Mirana leaps in a direction, giving her increased movement speed after"
	
	
	// Tinker
    "npc_dota_hero_tinker" "Tinker"
    "npc_dota_hero_tinker_bio" "Tinker is the ultimate fighting machine, with virtually no downtime on it's spells. Refreshing them has never been this easy, while having a heavy hurting package of spells at your disposal. Tracking rockets and Lasers! Need 
more convincing?"
	"AbilityTooltip_tinker_special_bottom" "Tinker launches two heat seaking rockets, despite them being slow and not everlasting they deal good damage." 
	"AbilityTooltip_tinker_special_side" "Tinker fires a laser to targets in his direction, dealing good damage to them. Takes cursor position into account."
	"AbilityTooltip_tinker_special_top" "Tinker refreshes it's spells like it's nothing. The only shame is that he won't be able to anything but moving for a while."
	
	
	// Nyx
    "npc_dota_hero_nyx_assassin" "Nyx Assassin"
    "npc_dota_hero_nyx_assassin_bio" "Nyx is the annoying disrupting creature it always is, better to be left alone. However it may strike unexpected with 
good force."
	"AbilityTooltip_nyx_assassin_special_top" "Nyx shields itself with earth, reflecting instances of damage for a short duration while jumping up." 
	"AbilityTooltip_nyx_assassin_special_side" "Nyx silences and damages the first target it sees. Takes cursor position into account."
	
	"AbilityTooltip_nyx_assassin_special_bottom" "Nyx impales his platform, stunning units and knocking them up. Doesn't work when not on a platform."
	
	// Axe
    "npc_dota_hero_axe" "Axe"
    "npc_dota_hero_axe_bio" "Axe might be the manliest manfighter there is, takes hits like noone else, but also knows how to throw a heavy punch. Does have several tricks to get into a fight, don't play Axe if you didn't come to fight!"
	"AbilityTooltip_axe_special_side" "Axe spins his axe around, damaging everyone around him." 
	"AbilityTooltip_axe_special_top" "Axe jumps up, preparing for the dunk! Deals heavy damage and refreshes when it hits a unit. Not the easiest but very satisfying! Takes cursor position into account."
	"AbilityTooltip_axe_special_bottom" "Axe taunts nearby enemies, they will follow him for a short duration while not being able to do anything else."
	
	// Venge
    "npc_dota_hero_vengefulspirit" "Venge"
    "npc_dota_hero_vengefulspirit_bio" "Venge is a classic dota hero, has a great stun, a clever swap and has a way do enhance damage by reducing armor." 
	"AbilityTooltip_vengefulspirit_special_side" "Venge throws his magic missile, stunning the target it hits. Takes cursor position into account."
	"AbilityTooltip_vengefulspirit_special_top" "Venge fires a projectile, when it hits it swap positions with that unit, if it does not hit Venge moves to the end. Takes cursor position into account."
	"AbilityTooltip_vengefulspirit_special_bottom" "Venge fires two armor reducing projectiles in both ways, deals minor damage"
	
	// Storm
    "npc_dota_hero_storm_spirit" "Storm"
    "npc_dota_hero_storm_spirit_bio" "Storm is the most mobile hero to be seen, zips with electric speed to drop his remnants or to grab and pull his foes." 
	"AbilityTooltip_storm_spirit_special_side" "Storm throws a projectile that damages on impact and grabs the target and pulls it closer towards."
	"AbilityTooltip_storm_spirit_special_top" "Storm zips in target direction. REQUIRES THE MOUSE TO BE 
HELD."
	"AbilityTooltip_storm_spirit_special_bottom" "Strom drops a remnant, exploding whenever it runs out or when an enemy is near."
	
	// Magnus
    "npc_dota_hero_magnataur" " Magnus"
    "npc_dota_hero_magnataur_bio" "Magnus is the ultimate position controller. Stun everyone around you with Reverse Polarity, or Skewer everyone along with you in a path to suffering, to finish it off, blow enemies away with a powerful shockwave" 
	"AbilityTooltip_magnataur_special_side" "Magnus casts his shockwave, hurting everything that gets into contact with it."
	"AbilityTooltip_magnataur_special_top" "Magnus skewers in target direction, pushing enemies with him. REQUIRES THE MOUSE TO BE HELD."
	"AbilityTooltip_magnataur_special_bottom" "Magnus reverses the polarity, stunning everyone around him and placing them all in front of him to finish the defenseless 
targets off."

// Phoenix
    "npc_dota_hero_phoenix" "Phoenix"
    "npc_dota_hero_phoenix_bio" "Phoenix does not have the legendary reviving skills he is know for, but has the power to burn enemies and smash them off with
his dives." 
	"AbilityTooltip_phoenix_special_side" "Phoenix throws one of his fire spirits in target direction, burning enemies who get hit by it."
	"AbilityTooltip_phoenix_special_top" "Phoenix dives forward in a arc to her location, and returning to it after. Can be cancelled by casting the spell again"
	"AbilityTooltip_phoenix_special_bottom" "Phoenix becomes her egg, loses all control and falls down. Deals damage to units it passes through and possible again if they hit the explosion on the platform. The damage from the explosion
also stuns."

// SF
    "npc_dota_hero_nevermore" "Shadow Fiend"
    "npc_dota_hero_nevermore_bio" "The classic show off hero comes with style in 2D as well. Landing a good requiem will be rewarded, and using all your razes will give you endless pleasure. Besides all that he has a simple yet useful blink dagger to get out of tricky situations." 
	"AbilityTooltip_nevermore_special_side" "Throw a raze, what kind of raze depends on the distance clicked from the center. Cast them all in succession and they will refresh. Cast one double and they all fail."
	"AbilityTooltip_nevermore_special_top" "Shadow Fiend blinks away in target direction, ready to position himself for another round."
	"AbilityTooltip_nevermore_special_bottom" "Shadow Fiend takes a long time to get ready, but when he is everyone will know. Throws projectiles in every direction!"
	
	// Pudge
    "npc_dota_hero_pudge" "Pudge"
    "npc_dota_hero_pudge_bio" "Everyones favorite butcher is a amazing at close range, and has ways to get his foes close to him." 
	"AbilityTooltip_pudge_special_side" "Hooks in target direction, grabbing the first unit it hits and dragging it closer."
	"AbilityTooltip_pudge_special_top" "Pudge exhumes his toxic gasses, while rising up in the air. Deals damage to enemies around him, and half to self."
	"AbilityTooltip_pudge_special_bottom" "Pudge grabs the first unit he sees and starts feeding from it. After completing the duration he tosses the unit away. Heals the damage he deals."

	// Batrider
    "npc_dota_hero_batrider" "Batrider"
    "npc_dota_hero_batrider_bio" "Batrider is here to burn the battlefield, grab your enemies, blow them up and put the map on fire!." 
	"AbilityTooltip_batrider_special_side" "Throws a molotov cocktail in target direction, dealing damage and knocking units back."
	"AbilityTooltip_batrider_special_top" "Spread your wings and burn everything left behind, deals decent damage when your foes are forced to
stay in the fire."
	"AbilityTooltip_batrider_special_bottom" "Batrider drops his lasso and grabs the first unit it sees and drags it along. Dragged units are stunned."
	
	// Centaur
    "npc_dota_hero_centaur" "Centaur"
    "npc_dota_hero_centaur_bio" "Pure strength is sometimes all it takes. If that's not enough Centaur also has great mobility with his 
Stampede" 
	"AbilityTooltip_centaur_special_side" "Strikes so hard in his direction that he doesn't only hurts his foes, but also himself."
	"AbilityTooltip_centaur_special_top" "Centaur rushes into a vicious charge moving extremely fast and hurting enemies he passes through "
	"AbilityTooltip_centaur_special_bottom" "Centaur stamps with his hoofs on the ground, stunning and damaging nearby targets."
	
	// Kunkka
    "npc_dota_hero_kunkka" "Kunkka"
    "npc_dota_hero_kunkka_bio" "The king of the sea is here to take advantage of the enviroment. Will it be enough?" 
	"AbilityTooltip_kunkka_special_side" "After a while a torrent pops up, damaging and stunning enemies."
	"AbilityTooltip_kunkka_special_top" "Kunkka blinks up and grabs his anchor making him unable to fall without moving."
	"AbilityTooltip_kunkka_special_bottom" "Kunkka calls his ghostship and makes sure it sets sail for destruction."
	
	// Techies
    "npc_dota_hero_techies" "Techies"
    "npc_dota_hero_techies_bio" "Techies have arrived and brought their entire arsenal of explosives with them. Be cautious though, techies might be used to explosives, they still hurt" 
	"AbilityTooltip_techies_special_side" "Techies throws out a rolling bomb, that ignites when techies wants to."
	"AbilityTooltip_techies_special_top" "Techies jumps up igniting his explosive mixture, upon landing techies explodes."
	"AbilityTooltip_techies_special_bottom" "Techies drops a mine below him, explodes whenever an enemy gets in contact."
}

